{
    "id": "weather",
    "name": "Shoji Funakawa",
    "yomi": "船川翔司",
    "text": [
        "Weathering with ..."
    ],
    "link": [
        {
            "a": "Website",
            "href": "http://sjfnkw.com/"
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "Shine",
            "jp": "ひかる",
            "yes": "bright",
            "left": "まぶしい",
            "no": "indistinct",
            "right": "よくみえない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "Blow",
            "jp": "ふく",
            "yes": "far ahead",
            "left": "とおくへ",
            "no": "in here",
            "right": "ここで"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "Heap up",
            "jp": "つもる",
            "yes": "being buried",
            "left": "埋まる",
            "no": "melt in mouse",
            "right": "口で溶ける"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "Being exposed",
            "jp": "うたれる",
            "yes": "run down on my cheek",
            "left": "頬を伝う",
            "no": "hold an umbrella",
            "right": "傘をさす"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "Hold up",
            "jp": "かざす",
            "yes": "cold",
            "left": "つめたい",
            "no": "warm",
            "right": "あたたかい"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "Being hit",
            "jp": "あたる",
            "yes": "burn",
            "left": "燃える",
            "no": "spark",
            "right": "萌える"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "Being covered",
            "jp": "おおわれる",
            "yes": "cool",
            "left": "涼しい",
            "no": "look out over",
            "right": "見渡す"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "Strain",
            "jp": "そばだてる",
            "yes": "fall",
            "left": "ふる",
            "no": "stopped",
            "right": "やんでいる"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "Get wet",
            "jp": "ぬれる",
            "yes": "heavy",
            "left": "おもい",
            "no": "light",
            "right": "かるい"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "Weathering with ...",
            "jp": "天気と共に",
            "yes": "in here",
            "left": "ここで",
            "no": "somewhere",
            "right": "どこかで"
        }
    ]
}